# ARTURO V. PACAÑA JR.

## **OBJECTIVE**

To obtain a position in the Information Technology industry and impart my vast experience knowledge and skills to an honorable organization.

#### SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS

Strong computer and networking support experience. Hardware and software installation, configuration and troubleshooting experience with client/server running Windows, Netware, Linux and OSX platforms; Cisco and Adtran routers and switches. Multi-tasking, detail oriented and able to make quick decisions in a fast-paced environment.

### **EXPERIENCE**

Jan 2005 – Nov 2020 National Cinemedia, Media Networks Northern/Central, CA *DCN Field Operations Technician* 

In-charge of all digital content network installation and maintenance.

Troubleshoot and fix on and off-site client/server, plasma/LCD, digital projector, switches, networks and several proprietary units.

Assist all theater managers and staff with issues related to Digital Content Network.

Performing audio, video and network Preventative Maintenance and Quality Assurance of preshow and digital equipment.

Roll out equipment and network install for new or converted sites.

Log & report day-to-day activities directly to our directors.

Assist organizers and patrons with their digital events, such as live concert, corporate prescreening and demo events.

Perform training to theater managers and staff regarding DCN responsibilities, functionality and its entirety.

Train and assist new field techs in my area.

Jul 2000 – Dec 2004 Signature Theatres Management Company San Ramon, CA Information Systems Technician/Junior Administrator

Manage corporate LAN/WAN, client/server running Windows, Netware, Linux and OSX platforms.

Setup and maintain file, DNS, Exchange/EMWAC mail and antivirus servers.

Install and manage theater POS terminals, data display, Protobase creditcard and voice servers.

Support corporate end-users and off-site managers desktop and laptop setup, upgrades and troubleshooting.

In charge of developing Norton Security Enterprise virus definition transport method via FTP to all remote servers thru various routers.

Perform Ghost imaging thru multiple machines, backup and disaster recovery applications.

Analyze and resolve credit card and ATM issues, such as fraud or software malfunctions, thru the carrier and processors.

#### **CERTIFICATION**

A+, Network+ certified.

## **EDUCATION**

1986–1989 Far Eastern University

Manila, Philippines

B.S. in Electrical Engineering

Special emphasis on electrical and electronic devices, including computers and telecommunications